natta.com 2008-04-17

# Natta Privacy Policy - natta!

Your privacy is important for us! Here at Natta we know how much you value your privacy, so we have taken the appropriate measures to ensure that your privacy is protected at any time you are using our services. To allow you to use our website and to process your orders and requests we need you to provide us some of your personal information. For that reason, we want you to know what information we need, why we need it, and how we will deal with it. In this document you will also find out what we do for your information to be protected ad to make sure that it will only be used for business purposes. By visiting our Site, you are signing your consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy. Minors can only use our Site with the consent and involvement of a parent or guardian.

1\. The Natta experience

By using the Natta website, you are expressly consenting to the information processing practices described in this policy. We want you to be able to enjoy your personalized journey here...a safe and private experience!

2\. Information we collect from you

2.1. Signing Up

When you sign up with Natta, you are requested to establish a password-protected personal account for all our services. During the account creation process and/or to place an order, we may need you to provide us certain “personal information”, namely contact and billing information (such as your mobile phone number). We use this information to provide you with our Services and to contact you about the items in which you have expressed interest. We can also collect "demographic and usage data" (i.e. information submitted by you or collected by Natta which are necessary for the proper operation and billing of the service, such as period and extent of your usage of the service).

2.2. Technical Information

The Natta website collects and retains technical information regarding visits to our website such as the IP address assigned to the computer visiting the site, the type of browser used by a visitor and the operating system running the user's connections to the service. This data is not linked to your personal account. It is used to analyze the ways in which our site is used, and how we can improve the user experience.

2.3. Cookies

In addition to the information which you supply to us, information an data may be automatically collected through the use of cookies. Cookies are small text files the website can use to recognise users and their visits to the website. We may also store information about you using cookies which we can access when you visit again the website. This will allow us to observe behaviour and compile aggregate data in order to improve your Natta experience. Cookies does not contain your personal data, such as your name, mobile phone number, e-mail address or postal code and we will not disclose the contact of cookies to any third parties.

3\. How we use your information

3.1. General use

Natta uses your personal information in the following general ways: to provide you with our Services, to allow your identification and authentication onto the Natta website, for billing and administrative functions; to contact you and for internal research and reporting purposes. We also use the information optionally provided by you in surveys for purposes of monitoring or improving the use of and satisfaction with our Services. Information about users' visits to this Site, such as the number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personally identifiable information), may be used to serve ads to users on this Site.

3.2. Disclosure of Personal Information to Third Parties

Although the personal information you provide us is an important part of our business we are not in the business of selling this information to others. This information will only be shared with our affiliated partners and agents when it is necessary and used to improve the quality and customize the Services we provide you. We may allow that third parties who provide website support services, billing, processing, fulfilment, marketing, and other services on our behalf access your personal information to provide those services only. We may also send you additional information about the Services, through the mobile phone number you provide.

3.3. Third Party Websites Appearing on our Site

The Natta website contains links and advertisements for sites operated by third parties whose policies regarding the handling of personal information may differ from ours. While we endeavour to associate only with reputable websites, Natta cannot be responsible for any information provide by you to these other websites. Any information you provide on those sites is subject to their privacy policies, and not this policy.

4\. Protecting your information

Natta uses industry best practices to protect your personal information and your privacy. When any personal information is requested on the site we use SSL to present secure pages to protect that. You can tell if you are using a secure server by looking at the bottom of your browser window. In Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer, you will see a lock icon. When the symbol is unbroken or the padlock appears to be in its closed state, the page is encrypted and therefore secure. Only a reduced number of professionals, obligated to confidentiality duties, shall have access to this information.

5\. Viewing and updating your account information

5.1. Right of Access

Under the applicable laws, the User has at any time the right of access to data, namely the right to the rectification, erasure or blocking of data concerning to himself. To update your personal information please contact our Support team by writing [support.us@natta.com ](mailto:support.us@natta.com). You can make changes to your account information at any time. Natta is allowed to transmit your “personal data” to the mobile phone service provider in order to secure the collection of fees. Furthermore, Natta is also allowed to transmit your personal information to governmental agencies, including but not limited to courts and district attorneys' offices, for legal proceedings and the prevention of crimes.

5.2. Contact Information

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us by phone at 1-800-331-3041 or by mail at [support.us@natta.com ](mailto:support.us@natta.com).

6\. Changes to this privacy policy

Natta reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to update, amend and/or change this Privacy Policy without prior notice at any time. Updates to this Privacy Policy will be posted here and will be immediately valid from that on. You are encouraged to revisit this Privacy Policy from time to time in order to review any changes that have been made. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. By continuing to use the site after changes to this policy, you agree to these changes.

7\. Ownership and data control

7.1. Data Controller

The Data Controller for all purposes of this document is TOTAL TIM – Serviços de Telecomunicações Móveis e Afins, Lda. a company within TIMw.e. Group and established under Portuguese Law, with its headquarters at Edifício Amoreiras Square, Rua Joshua Benoliel, nº1 – 3ºC 1250 – 273 LISBON - PORTUGAL. The Data Controller may jointly process the information with its affiliates around the world that may collect your personal information on behalf of the Data Controller. Personal data collected by Natta may be stored and processed in the USA or any other country in which Natta or its agents maintain facilities, and the transmission of the information outside of your country is expressly accepted by you when you use Natta. Natta is abide to and shall respect Portuguese and the European Commission Data Protection legislation that shall be able to assure adequate protection and high security levels on the processing of your personal data.

7.2. Dispute Resolution

Any complaints or disputes related to your personal data gathered and stored by Natta shall be submitted by e-mail at [support.us@natta.com ](mailto:support.us@natta.com) to Edifício Amoreiras Square, Rua Carlos Alberto Mota Pinto, no. 17 - 6B 1070-313 LISBOA - PORTUGAL and will be investigated and resolved by the Data Controller.
